This movie's called Project Handmary.
And uh it's very good and the character
he acts he acts kind of uh like he
doesn't know anything in the movie. But
then after a while he kind of
learns how to do everything in the movie
and it's very good and there's also a
book of it if you're interested in the
book. It looks like this.
But I haven't I haven't read the book
yet but I have watched the movie.
And the movie is very good and uh
as you can see uh there's the back right
there.
And there there's the front.
There's the front.
And the movie is very good and I'm
hoping there's going to be a second
movie of this coming out because the
movie was quite good. And there's a lot
they can do with just going to be a part
two of this movie.
And I won't spoil it for anybody but uh
yeah if you it's a very good movie.
And there's special features in this as
well and deleted scenes on this one.
This is a Blu-ray.
And I got it second hand as you can see.